Excuse me, sir. Question for you.
If you were to go back in time
and have a conversation with your younger self
when you were starting from zero,
what's the best piece of advice
that you would tell your younger self?
Fail faster and don't make it mean fucking shit.
Find mentors and model their behaviors.
In what industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
I originally started my business in social media marketing,
and that's how I made my first million dollars.
Commercial real estate.
Well, I'm a professional soccer player.
I'm actually a spymaster.
We just landed in Miami, Florida,
and we're asking Miami millionaires how they became wealthy.
What has been the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
Four million.
In what industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
Multiple industries, but
ultimately business development, sales,
and I've been a vice president
for years, have my own business now,
but fixing companies and growing their sales.
What was the best financial advice
that you ever received throughout your lifetime?
A friend of mine on Wall Street, I said,
take 10% of your income, put
it in a stock index fund,
and all your other investments are outside of that.
Follow that strictly.
How can someone really scale
their business in today's world?
What's the secret to scaling?
Well, I think there's three.
Three levels of scaling.
There's your initial, which is a
lot of blood, sweat, and tears.
Second is, what's your second term look like?
Your second hundred million is not going to
be the same as your third hundred million.
Where's it going to come from?
What does that require?
And a lot of people misestimate
the initial first, second, and third tranches.
So thinking through that and having experts around
you to do that, I think is helpful.
How do you get from
a seven to an eight-figure business?
Assessing your market.
What is your green field?
What is your, do you
really understand where you could go?
In other words, maybe your
market isn't prepared to go there,
but if your market is, really
thinking through how do you get there?
Because your first million could be lucky.
It could be friends and family.
It could be, I had a
good idea, but it's not scalable.
So understanding that next level is
saying, is there a market, number one?
And if there's a huge
market, then what's the right approach?
And getting the right people to
tell you how to get there.
Like, what do you think?
Just not trying to figure out on your own.
Thank you so much, sir.
I really appreciate that.
Have a great day, sir.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much, sir.
Fucking impressive.
What's the name of this head again?
The School of Hard Knocks.
By the way, don't trust anything this guy says.
Ah, cheese and crackers.
He is absolutely great.
No, we were walking by, I'm like,
oh my God, Jim Sheridan's being interviewed.
We have to watch this.
No, I don't have any good advice to young people.
It's not YOLO anymore, it's YODO.
Could we get this one?
Just this one.
All right, let me do it.
Let's do it.
What industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
I'm actually a spymaster.
Like, what exactly do you do on it?
It's called competitive intelligence.
So essentially, I look at what's going
on in the external environment of a company,
same way that a government would
look at external threats, internal threats.
That's where competitive intelligence really comes in.
What's the best financial advice you ever received?
Pay yourself first.
And that goes to your retirement.
Because Social Security, I'm 52 years old.
Social Security is probably not going to be
around when I get to be 70 or 65.
So the best piece of advice was from my dad.
Pay yourself first.
Look at what's going on.
Where is there traction?
And then invest in there.
It's not a fly-by-night company.
You've got to look at where there's traction.
Then that's where you're going to invest.
What is your best advice to anybody
starting out in the real world today?
So there was a big thing with millennials.
It was YOLO.
You only live once.
But when you really think about it, you
live every day and you only die once.
So.
If you only die once, which is YOLO, you should
live every day like it's going to be your last.
Like you will die tomorrow.
So don't put off today what
you could miss out on tomorrow.
And that's the whole concept of YOLO.
What's going on, guys?
A few weeks ago, we had met
a super sick entrepreneur who lives in Miami.
He's a multimillionaire sales guy.
And man, he's got some crazy game.
He told us to pull up to the apartment.
So we're about to go through to his
penthouse in Miami, shoot a quick interview with him.
And let's see what he has to say.
How are you?
Oh, your partner's here.
How are you doing, man?
Good to see you.
Hey, Jeff.
Nice to meet you, man.
What made you decide to move to Miami?
It's the lack of deprecation around working too much.
I think too often in smaller cities and sleepier
cities, there's too much deprecating people for working too much.
There's shaming around.
You're not balancing your lifestyle.
Whereas.
Here.
I finally feel accepted for wanting to work
till 10 or 11 or till 3 a.m.
I think that's the greatest thing of what
motivated me, inspired me to move to Miami.
You could go into a room where you're the smartest person in the room, and
then you could literally leave in an hour later and be in a coffee shop.
And there's a billionaire there, right?
The exposure to wealth and how
many levels there are to the game.
It constantly keeps you aware that you just need to
keep working because transformation is a mountain with no top.
And when you're around people that are.
Thinking bigger, it creates this environment and
container that pushes what's possible for you.
That makes sense.
That's what I love about Miami.
If you were to go back in time and have a conversation with your younger self when
you were starting from zero, what's the best piece of advice that you would tell your younger self?
Fail faster and don't make it mean fucking shit.
I think too many people think that
they're like attached to some sort of result.
They have to have it be some way.
They think that if it doesn't go a certain way that they're going to
like fail and this like the end of the world is going to happen.
Right?
And so I think people create so
much significance in the very, very small failures.
When you look at Israel as a country per capita and how many businesses have flourished into
the billion unicorn startup, they have way more billion dollar unicorn startups than any other country combined.
Why is that?
One thing they teach their kids is just failing forward intelligently, learning
from their mistakes faster and compounding time and removing the significance of everything.
So if I could go back to the beginning,
I would say, hey, I'm going to be a billionaire.
I'm going to be a billionaire.
I'm going to go back to
my young self and give advice.
Dude, fail fucking faster and it doesn't mean shit.
A mentor that I've really researched
and understood his materials, Ryan Breslow.
The guy is under 30 years old and he
owns two now almost three multi-billion dollar unicorn startups.
Two things that I learned is that
it comes down to fundraising and recruiting.
I think too many people don't realize that how much cash
you actually need to scale and you can only generate that cash.
And scale and hire when you have good leadership.
And you can only have good leadership
when you have really good visionary skills.
And you can only have really good visionary
skills if you have a really good product.
People will tell you, oh, it's got to have one product on one platform that
you scale with one ad and then you scale from there by adding more products.
That might be true in an e-commerce business.
But if we're talking about raw financial services, if we're talking about
banking and private equity, it all comes down to top tier talent.
In tech, it's all top tier.
It's all top tier talent.
That's why the unicorn startups go
and steal the talent from other companies.
It's really talent.
But you cannot have talent
without really good compensation packages.
And you can't have good compensation packages if
you don't have a badass product that sells itself.
Well, I got to say, Johnny may have one
of the craziest departments that I've ever been to.
He was super nice to let us come through, give us some game for the young
entrepreneurs and how he was able to become super successful and wealthy out here in Miami, Florida.
We just made it to Brickell where we're going to go ask some more multimillionaires out
here how they became successful and how you can start your path to becoming financially free.
And we're going to talk
about that in a little bit.
But before we go, let's talk about the industry.
I'm going to talk about the industry.
So, I'm going to talk about the industry.
And I'm going to talk about the industry.
And what industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
IT.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, I'm a software engineer.
Yeah, yeah.
So, you're working right now?
Well, I work for myself.
Yeah, I own my own company.
I build apps for Penn State University, Lockheed Martin.
I actually did apps for the state of Texas.
What was the most amount of money
that you ever made in a single year?
I would say about $2 million.
How important has it been surrounding yourself
with the right people throughout your career?
Relationships is everything.
You know, every city I go in, I try
to build with the who's who in the city.
I try to find people
that I can offer something to.
So, whenever you want to develop a relationship
with somebody, when you sit down with somebody,
you come to the table with something to offer.
You know, make sure you can
trade off a balance or whatever.
My last question for you.
What was the best financial advice
that you ever received throughout your lifetime?
Learning how to leverage your credit.
You know, that means that you can save your cash.
And pretty much, you know,
just understanding the whole 70-30 rule.
Whatever you earn, you know,
you want to be able to
save 70% of it and
pretty much operate off of 30%.
As long as you keep that algorithm, you
know, you'll see yourself growing and growing and growing.
What's up, guys?
What's up, man?
How are you?
Rene, nice to meet you.
Gabe.
Nice to meet you.
Jack.
Josh, man. Nice to meet you.
Rene, nice to meet you.
What industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
I originally started my business in social media marketing.
And that's how I made my first million dollars.
And then eventually, while I'm
running this agency for people,
I realized I didn't like talking to clients.
It was a lot of work.
People were mean to me.
Even though I was technically running my business,
it was really difficult for me
to swallow the fact that, like,
even though I have my own business,
people are still telling me what to do.
So eventually I said, you know what?
I'm doing this for all these other people.
Let me just start my own brand.
And from there, I started my e-commerce brands.
I own a supplement company and
I built another big e-commerce brand.
What do you think is the significance
and the importance of really building
a strong brand for a company?
Well, the thing about a brand is eventually
at some point you tell someone to jump.
They ask you how high.
There's not even a question of why should I jump?
Where should I jump? Why am I jumping?
It's
a
lot of people.
It's like, how high do you want me to jump?
And Apple has built a brand so
powerful that no matter what they release,
they can release a shoe, a T-shirt,
a key chain.
People will buy it.
They will sell millions of them.
If you take a look at headphones, AirPods,
they don't make that much money off AirPods.
I want to say it's not that much money.
It's still billions of dollars because they built
a brand that is so powerful, so strong.
They can release any product and people would buy it.
And what has been the most amount of
money that you ever made in a single year?
Me or my businesses?
Both.
Okay, so the most money I
personally made in a single year,
I did $3.5 million in a single year for myself.
The businesses that year did about $14 million.
For someone who's starting out in e-commerce today,
what would be your best piece of advice
for them?
You have to figure out the winning product.
At the end of the day, when it comes
to e-commerce, if you're going to start from nothing, the
easiest way to make money
in e-commerce is not the marketing.
People think it's running Facebook
ads and getting good marketing.
It's not that.
It's always going to be the product.
Your product will sell over everything.
It goes product, marketing, sales.
So if your product is good, you don't need marketing.
If your marketing is good, you don't need sales.
But if you have all three of them.
That's how you get rich.
I don't have an Apple computer.
I have just a regular one just because
my friends that make a lot of money, they're
like, you don't need a Mac.
You just need this.
You need the internet.
That's it.
And then I see everyone with Macs.
I'm like, why do you guys all have Macs?
And they're like, because it's better.
I was like, well, how is it better?
And the guy was like, well, uh, uh,
and he couldn't like, he was literally sitting there
trying to think of reasons why it was better.
And I was like, and I
let him talk for like five minutes.
I'm like, why is it better?
He's like, uh, uh, I don't know.
And I was like, you know why it's better?
Cause they got you with a random, what's
one thing that Miami is, has just done for
your mindset.
I just want to level up, man.
I mean, we're based out of Austin, but the
more I've been here, it's like, damn, I got
to hustle harder.
So now I can have my HQ spot in Austin.
But then when I want to go
work in paradise, I go to Miami.
This is not a real place.
I'm convinced.
Like this is, this is literally not a real place.
I mean, you just got people driving
exotic lips, people partying during the day.
You got people just lounging around in beaches.
Like everyone's just like having a great time here.
It just doesn't even seem,
it just seems like utopia here.
In Miami.
What industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
Well, I'm a professional soccer player.
Professional soccer player.
Yeah.
I play in Germany.
Do you actually?
What team do you play for?
I play for Victoria Cal.
I'm in the fourth division.
That's incredible.
I'm like scaling.
What has been the biggest driving factor of
your success that it's allowed you to become
a professional soccer player overseas?
To put my whole family on my back.
I like pressure.
And like when I put people on
my back, like I perform my best.
So, so yeah.
Let's say even like young adults, maybe 25,
26 years old, they're stuck in a job right
now that they may not have any
passion or desire to go to work.
And they're kind of struggling.
At that point, what's your advice to people
that kind of are not feeling fulfilled at
work?
Quit and chase happiness.
You can't put a price on unhappiness.
And if you're really unhappy at a job,
I don't think you can, you can work.
Find your passion.
If you're 30, it's fine.
And you don't have a passion.
Try to find it.
Try everything.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
If you were to go back in time
and have a conversation with your younger self, when
you were starting from zero, what's the best
piece of advice that you would tell your younger
self?
Ask a lot of questions,
find mentors and model their behaviors.
Whatever it is you want to
do in life, it's already been done.
Find someone who's already done it.
Follow what they did.
For you personally though, like how important
has it been surrounding yourself with the
right people throughout your career?
It's been unlimited possibilities for me.
It's the most important thing you could do.
In what industry did you ultimately pursue a career in?
Commercial real estate with property managers
and developers and commercial properties throughout
South Florida.
In your opinion, how can someone really
break into commercial real estate in today's world?
Oh, my friend, that's going to
take a little bit of time.
So if you want the real answer, follow me in.
I'll show you.
Why did you choose this location?
Because for us in the real estate
business, this building is centrally located between
two highways.
So there's I-95.
I-95 to the east and the Florida Turnpike
to the west, which allows us easy access to
all our properties.
All of our properties are within a
driving distance of three hours or less.
So from here, we can hit them real quick.
Could you tell me that story again that
you were like mentioning earlier about like this
building and like how it came about?
So this building is an interesting building.
And you know, a lot of people nowadays, the
fancy thing to talk about is the office market
is dead and everybody shouldn't invest in office.
This building shows you an alternate
route to making money and investing.
The guy who owns this building was
a billionaire when he bought this building.
He made it in the pharmaceutical business.
Fast forward, he bought like
five or six buildings like this.
Even this one included is not fully occupied.
However, in one of his buildings in Boca Raton,
where he uses his office, he has a tenant
there who wanted to be in the energy drink business.
This guy started a company and couldn't make it work.
The owner of this building met him
and knew logistics better, bought his company from
him.
Fast forward a couple of years, that Celsius
water went public and made billions of dollars
again.
Never would have happened if
he didn't own the office building.
But from owning that building, he met that client.
There you go.
You can make money any
way you want if you're entrepreneurial.
What was the best financial advice
that you've ever received throughout your lifetime?
Don't count other people's money.
And so many people are looking at other
people and they're seeing things that really aren't
real.
But a lot of this stuff isn't real and
people get so caught up in what other people have
and keeping up with the Joneses and
they're buying things and spending money on things
they really can't afford.
And I don't want to say stay
in your lane, but worry about yourself.
Worry about if you're good.
So much of what the young
people are doing is not good.
And I think that's what the young
generation sees today all over the place.
It's fake.
And they know it's fake, but they see it
and they think it's real and they're trying to
keep up.
You start comparing yourself to other people,
there's always going to be someone richer.
There's always going to be someone faking it more.
It'll make you feel insecure because
you're going to go right now.
I could go with you on Instagram and
show you a thousand kids that look like they're
doing great and it could
make you feel bad about yourself.
Worry about yourself.
Go at your own pace and it'll work out fine.
And one more thing, be sure to leave
a like and subscribe for tons of amazing content
coming soon.